Eat better, live better & help save the planet.
Food Choices is a documentary film directed by Michal Siewierski.
This documentary explores the impact that food choices have on people's health,
the health of our planet and on the lives of other living species.
And also discusses several misconceptions about food and diet.
Self - Wellness Forum, played by Pam Popper.
Self - Professor Emeritus of Biochemistry, played by T. Colin Campbell.
Self - Wellness Advocate, played by Joe Cross.
Self - Eco-Lifestyle Expert, played by Ashlee Piper.
Self - Physician, Nutrition Expert, played by John McDougall.
Self - NutritionFacts.org, played by Michael Greger.
Ghostbusters (also known as Ghostbusters: Answer the Call) is a 2016 American
supernatural comedy film directed by Paul Feig, who co-wrote it with Katie Dippold.
Starring Melissa McCarthy, Kristen Wiig, Leslie Jones, Kate McKinnon, and Chris Hemsworth, it
is a reboot of the 1984 film and the third film in the Ghostbusters franchise.
The story focuses on four eccentric women who start a ghost-catching
business in New York City after a paranormal encounter.
A third Ghostbusters film had been in various stages of development
following the release of Ghostbusters II in 1989.
Sony Pictures rebooted the series following the death of the original cast member Harold Ramis in
2014, and because another cast member, Bill Murray, refused to commit to a sequel.
Some of the original cast and their family members make cameos in new
roles, and Ramis is commemorated in the film's closing credits.
The announcement of the female-led cast in 2015 drew a
polarized response from the public.
Ghostbusters premiered at the TCL Chinese Theatre in Los Angeles on July 9, 2016, and
was released in the United States on July 15, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film grossed $229 million worldwide against a $144 million production budget,
making it a box-office bomb with losses for the studio of over $70 million.
Sony abandoned plans for a sequel, opting instead to continue the
original film canon with Ghostbusters: Afterlife (2021).
The film explores themes of diet, vegetarian, vegetable, health, animal rights.